<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on hooliganny</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on hooliganny</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 20:54:03 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future Projects</title>
      <link>/posts/future-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 20:54:03 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/future-projects/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I have a few projects planned. Once they are started, they will go here. Once they are complete, they will get their own page.
Current projects This site I currently am in the process of creating a home/title/about me page. I will also fix up the &amp;lsquo;Tags&amp;rsquo; page(s).
Doomsday Rule I am currently working on a Doomsday Rule website that will lead the user through the process needed to calculate any date of the calendar in their head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SafeFood4U Website</title>
      <link>/posts/safefood4u-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 19:34:47 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/safefood4u-website/</guid>
      <description>Over my summer break after my last year of university (2022), I worked off and on creating a portfolio website for my father&amp;rsquo;s family business.
Although I&amp;rsquo;m not the greatest graphic designer, this opportunity gave me the chance to showcase what I had learnt in over university, develop some appreciation for CSS, as well as grow my design skills (and also kept me from getting bored over a long break).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Matched</title>
      <link>/posts/project-matched/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 18:41:56 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/project-matched/</guid>
      <description>Originally done in my last semester at the University of Auckland (July 2022 to November 2022).
Overview For my capstone course, alongside 4 others, we built a responsive PWA that would link students from across the STEM faculties to projects that are owned by other students. These projects would be auto recommended by the backend through the user&amp;rsquo;s interests and skills that they filled out as a part of the signup process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 21:16:24 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>The site Welcome to my mini-blog, here I will post any significant updates to my portfolio. Each post will have corresponding tags, and links to the right places (if applicable).
My hope is that this site will act as a place where I can both see my growth, as well as showcase it to others.
This site is made in Hugo, a Go based static site generator. While I know the basics of Hugo, I decided against trying to reinvent the wheel and instead just used a premade theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
